Right now, begin to cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus.
Cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus.
The Blood of Jesus
The Blood of Jesus sets me free
From sin and sorrow
Whatever chain satan might have used to connect you -
be it your weaknesses -
whatever chain satan might have used to connect you to himself -
be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips and begin to disconnect yourself.
Disconnect yourself from satan.
Disconnect yourself!
Whatever chain satan might have used to connect you to himself,
to connect your business to himself,
to connect your career to himself,
to connect your marriage to himself,
to connect your life to himself - be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
I disconnect you, in the name of Jesus!
Be free!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The bank of everything is from Heaven.
Whatever challenges you are going through right now, I see you free, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever challenges you are in - I can see you being free, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being free, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Career failure,
affliction,
setback,
stagnation -
whatever challenges you are in - I can see you being free, in the name of Jesus!
When Jesus says, "Yes", no one can say, "No".
Don't forget the same anointing that said to the woman,
"You have not been seeing your menstruation for a while,
right now, go and check - your menstruation has come"
and the woman immediately saw her menstruation.
Whatever challenges you are in -
I can see your freedom!
Whatever challenges you are in - be it nightmare, career failure, stagnation, rejection, hardship -
whatever challenges you are going through, whatever challenges you are in -
I can see your freedom!
The way out for you has come!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
What could be the challenges?
Depression, affliction in your blood, bones, kidneys or in your liver -
never a sickness Jesus cannot cure.
Never an affliction Jesus cannot heal.
Never a burden Jesus cannot bear.
Whatever challenges, situation you are in - I can see your freedom!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can see your breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
I said I want to celebrate Easter with you.
There is no other way to celebrate it than to give you your salvation.
Salvation means to be set free.
And once you are set free, all other things -
breakthrough, blessing, healing, freedom will be added!
I can see your breakthrough!
Say, breakthrough!
Breakthrough - in my career!
Breakthrough - in my business!
Breakthrough - in my family!
Breakthrough - in my health!
Breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You will never forget this Easter because of what will follow!
You will never forget this Easter because of what follows!
What follows?
Breakthrough!
In Jesus Christ's name.
Rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Put your hands together! Come on!
Get ready!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chain of affliction
Oh oh
Break the chain of sorrow
Break the chain of poverty in your family
Oh oh
Break the chain of sorrow
Break the chain of curses
Just break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break
Oh oh
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chain of trouble
Oh oh
Break the chain of curses
Break the chain of poverty in your family
Oh oh
Break the chain of affliction
Break the chain of curses
Just break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break
Oh oh
Multiple Fibroids Burst
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Come on, this way!
Break
Oh oh
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Break the chains in your life
Not by power not by might
By the Spirit of the Lord
Break the chain
Can you see the chains falling
In the name of Jesus
I can see the chains falling
Can you see the chains falling
In the name of Jesus
I can see the chains falling
Can you see the chains falling
In the name of Jesus
I can see the chains falling
Can you hear the chains falling
In the name of Jesus
I can hear the chains falling
Can you hear the chains falling
In the name of Jesus
The SCOAN Sunday Service
My name is Blessing Okey Odazi.
I came from Delta State.
Just like the man of God prophesied to me that the fibroid will surely come out.
As we were singing worship songs, I felt a sensation and saw blood gushing out.
I came because of the multiple fibroids I have been having for the past eight years.
I have tried many things but nothing helped.
Today, I decided to come to The SCOAN. Praise God!
I thank God what He has done in my life.
How do you feel now that the fibroid is coming out?
I felt restless so I kept moving but I am okay now.
So if your own fibroid can come out,
because the man of God said, you have a fibroid and that fibroid will come out,
and the man of God has also said everyone's chain has been broken,
what do you think has happened to everyone?
Everybody's chain will be broken too, in Jesus' name!
My chain has broken today, in Jesus' name!
Everybody's own is broken too, in Jesus' name!
Multiple Fibroids Burst
Healed Of Multiple Fibroids
TT: Mel Flowers 28/04/2019